Guide to the Caroline Furness Papers, 1840-1938
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Photographs, circa 1870-1926, undated
  - Vassar College Observatory apartment, undated; [6 photographs] (Folder 4.25)
  - Whitney, Mary Watson, undated; [4 photographs] (Folder 4.26)
  - Whitney, Mary Watson with Caroline Furness and others, 1890, 1909, undated; [11 photographs] (Folder 4.27)
  - Unidentified individuals and groups, undated; [26 photographs] (Folder 4.28)
- Series V. Vassar Family Research, 1926-1932
  - Correspondence
    - Ambler, Alice to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928; [12 letters] (Folder 4.29)
    - Barnaby, E. L. to Furness, Caroline, 1928-1929; [4 letters] (Folder 4.30)
    - Bernau, R. and Charles to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928-1931; [10 letters] (Folder 4.31)
    - Galloway, L.M. to Furness, Caroline, 1927-1928; [3 letters] (Folder 4.32)
    - Hallinan, Hazel to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928; [3 letters] (Folder 4.33)
    - Harwood, Margaret to Furness, Caroline (including 3 transcribed letters from Matthew Vassar to Maria Mitchell and 1 transcribed lecture by Maria Mitchell), 1929; [2 letters, 3 transcribed letters, 1 transcribed lecture] (Folder 4.34)
    - Malerby, [Mrs.] to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928 May-Aug; [2 letters] (Folder 4.35)
    - Miscellaneous to Furness, Caroline, 1926-1932; [21 letters] (Folder 4.36)
    - Mottram, R. H. from Furness, Caroline, 1928 Mar-May; [2 letters] (Folder 4.37)
    - Schwab, Mildred to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928 Oct-Nov; [2 letters] (Folder 4.38)
    - Various to Furness, Caroline concerning Matthew Vassar portraits, 1927-1928; [6 letters] (Folder 4.39)
    - Vassar, William A. F. (and Fred Johnson) to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928-1931; [10 letters] (Folder 4.40)
    - Vores, B. H. to and from Furness, Caroline, 1928; [4 letters, 1 report] (Folder 4.41)
  - Notes
    - Matthew Vassar family, circa 1928 (Folders 4.42-4.43)
    - Vassar family and property, circa 1928 (Folder 4.44)
  - Research
    - Transcribed documents, circa 1928 (Folder 4.45)
    - Vassar, Matthew, Jr. - Diary (1890-1931), circa 1928; [transcript] (Folder 4.46)
  - Writings
    - Ambler, Alice, "Matthew Vassar's French Huguenot Ancestry," Vassar Quarterly, 1928 Nov (Folder 4.47)
    - Furness, Caroline, "Matthew Vassar's Family," Vassar Quarterly, 1928 Nov (Folder 4.48)